<note>
<date>2023-02-02</date>
<time>14:30</time>
<to>Recruiter</to>
<from>Katie</from>
<heading>Seeking Technical Writer Positions</heading>
<body>

February 2st, 2023

To Whom it May Concern,
 
In today’s fast-paced market, employers seek strong and dependable employees who are adaptable to ever
changing work environments. As you work toward your always shifting business growth objectives, I'm
confident that I can provide the traits you look for in a valuable employee. I have strong time management,
problem solving and prioritization skills, and strong logic and analysis skills. I have been working on my skills to
become a more attractive candidate for a technical writer position. You can find my upskill progression at
https://github.com/katiemarqueling/Career.

Sadly, I was forced to cut my law enforcement career short due to my severe allergy to the active ingredient in
pepper spray. I regret that I won’t be able to serve my community in the way I had envisioned, but I also
recognize the tremendous opportunities outside of city government. Since my Freshman year of college, I’ve
lived with my boyfriend and our mutual friends, who all had a background in Computer Science. I’ve long had
an interest in their fields of study, but not as a practitioner, rather as a translator. I quickly found out that there is
value in the interface between the developers who just want to write code and be left alone, and the customer,
who wants to feel like they’re talking to a human being who listens and understands their concerns. That’s the
value I hope to provide to your organization.

Given the opportunity to meet, you are certain to find me to be friendly and professional in nature. This allows
me to communicate with all levels of employees, including the end-user, project teams, operation managers,
and control partners. I look forward to learning more about your company, its plans and goals, and how I might
contribute to its continued success.
 
Respectfully,

Katie Marqueling

</body>
</note>